Guide to the Diane Sands Papers 1892-2000 (Bulk: 1964-2000)
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Women’s Studies at the University of Montana, 1964-1999; Series III; 0.8 linear feet
  - Courses, History and Politics of Feminism Course Materials, 1981 (Box-folder 9/14)
  - Courses, Women’s Studies Papers, 1981 (Box-folder 9/15)
  - Courses, Graduate Project Paper on Abortion Rights, Kristie L. Kirby, 1981 (Box-folder 9/16)
  - Courses, Women and Social Work – SW195, 1983 (Box-folder 9/17)
  - Courses, Women’s Studies Papers and Finals, 1985 (Box-folder 9/18)
  - Courses, Watson Scholarship Application, Nancy L. Arnold, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 9/19)
  - Courses, Introduction to Women’s Studies Course, undated (Box-folder 9/20)
  - Courses, Social Welfare 489 Course, undated (Box-folder 9/21)
  - Courses, Women Cross-Cultural Perspectives Bibliography, undated (Box-folder 9/22)
  - Courses, Bibliographies on Various Topics Regarding Women’s Issues, undated (Box-folder 9/23)
  - Courses, Materials Regarding Women’s Feminist Issues, undated (Box-folder 9/24)
  - Discrimination, Union Committee on Discrimination, Minutes, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 10/1)
  - Discrimination, Department of Health, Education and Welfare, Report on Discrimination, 1972 (Box-folder 10/2)
  - Discrimination, Materials Regarding Discrimination at University of Montana, 1972, 1973 (Box-folder 10/3)
  - Employment Practices, University of Montana, 1994 (Box-folder 10/4)
  - Employment Practices, Equal Opportunity Program, undated (Box-folder 10/5)
  - History, 1964-1971 (Box-folder 10/6)
  - History, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 10/7)
  - History, 1975-1999 (Box-folder 10/8)
  - History, undated (Box-folder 10/9)
  - History, undated (Box-folder 10/10)
  - Papers, Conference Papers on Feminist Therapy, 1974 (Box-folder 10/11)
  - Publications, "Anti-Feminist," Articles from the Missoulian on "Pussycat League", 1971 (Box-folder 10/12)
  - Publications, University of Montana Faculty and Staff Newsletters, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 10/13)
  - Publications, "Faculty Women’s Caucus", 1972-1973 (Box-folder 10/14)
  - Publications, Newspaper Clippings, Articles, and Furies Newsletter, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 10/15)
  - Publications, The NRAG Papers Publication, 1984 (Box-folder 10/16)
  - Publications, UM Magazine and Editorial Regarding Women’s Studies Program, 1999 (Box-folder 10/17)
  - The Political Economy of Women’s Liberation, undated (Box-folder 10/18)
- Montana Pro-Choice Coalition, 1971-1995; Series IV; 1.0 linear foot
  - Administrative Records, 1971-1989; Subseries 1; 0.6 linear feet
    - Abortion: For Survival, 1 videocassette, undated (Box-folder 25/1)
    - Boston Women’s Health Course Collective, 1971 (Box-folder 11/1)
    - Celebrations, Freedom Celebration Day, 1981 (Box-folder 11/2)
    - Committees, Steering Committee, 1979 (Box-folder 11/3)
    - Committees, Missoula Chapter, undated (Box-folder 11/4)
    - Correspondence, 1979 (Box-folder 11/5)
    - Correspondence, Letters from Montana Representatives to their Constituents, 1981 (Box-folder 11/6)
    - Correspondence, "1000 Pro-Choice Letter Campaign", undated (Box-folder 11/7)
    - Elections, Primary Election, 1982 (Box-folder 11/8)
    - Elections, Voting Records, undated (Box-folder 11/9)
    - Legislation, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 11/10)
    - Legislation, 1981 (Box-folder 11/11)
    - Legislation, 1981 (Box-folder 11/12)
    - Legislation, 1981 (Box-folder 11/13)
    - Legislation, 1981 (Box-folder 11/14)
    - Legislation, 1981 (Box-folder 11/15)
    - Legislation, 1981 (Box-folder 11/16)
    - Legislation, 1981 (Box-folder 11/17)
    - Legislation, undated (Box-folder 11/18)
    - Legislation, undated (Box-folder 11/18)
    - Legislative Packet, 1978 (Box-folder 11/19)
    - Legislative Packet, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 11/20)
    - Legislative Testimony, 1979 (Box-folder 11/21)
    - Legislature, Overview and Evaluation, 1981 (Box-folder 11/22)
    - Lobbying Notebook, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 12/1)
    - Lobbying Notebook, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 12/2)
    - Lobbying Notebook, undated (Box-folder 12/3)
    - March for Women’s Lives, Washington DC, In Other Words, 1 audiocassette, 1989 (Box-folder 25/2)
    - March for Women’s Lives, Washington DC, 1 videocassette, 1989 (Box-folder 25/3)
    - Montana Pro-Choice Coalition Materials, 1974-1981 (Box-folder 12/4)
    - Montana Pro-Choice Coalition Materials, 1981, 1989 (Box-folder 12/5)
    - Montana Pro-Choice Coalition Materials, undated (Box-folder 12/6)
    - Montana Pro-Choice Coalition Membership Lists, 1980 (Box-folder 12/7)
    - Photographs and Memorabilia, Contact Sheet of Photos and Pro-Choice Pins, 1981 (Box-folder 12/8)
    - Publications, Birth Control Handbook, 1972 (Box-folder 12/9)
    - Publications, Reproductive Rights Newsletter, 1978 (Box-folder 12/10)
    - Publications, Articles Regarding Abortion Rights, 1978-1989 (Box-folder 12/11)
    - Publications, House Meeting Training Packet, 1981 (Box-folder 12/12)
    - Publications, Montana Pro-Choice Newsletters, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 12/13)
    - Publications, Pamphlets and Flyers, NARAL and Abortion Control Act, undated (Box-folder 12/14)
  - Abortion, 1973-1995; Subseries 2; 0.4 linear feet
    - Blue Mountain Clinic, Escort Manual, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 12/15)
    - Minutes, Campaign for Repeal of Montana Abortion Control Act, 1984 (Box-folder 12/16)
    - Minutes, Montana Pro-Choice Advocates, 1985 (Box-folder 12/17)
    - Correspondence, 1982, 1983 (Box-folder 12/18)
    - Legislation, undated (Box-folder 12/19)
    - Legislature, 1985 (Box-folder 12/20)
    - Montanans for Choice, Survey, 1984 (Box-folder 12/21)
    - Petitions, 1986 (Box-folder 12/22)
    - Publications, Abortion, 1978-1993 (Box-folder 13/1)
    - Publications, Abortion, 1978-1983 (Box-folder 13/2)
    - Publications, Montana Legislature, 1985 (Box-folder 13/3)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1981-1993 (Box-folder 13/4)
    - Posters and Flyers, 1973-1982 (Box-folder 13/5)
    - Drawings, Self Portraits of Activists, undated (Box-folder 13/6)
- Women’s Liberation, 1954-1982; Series V; 1.6 linear feet
  - Homemakers/House Workers, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 13/7)
  - Lesbian History File, 1976-1981 (Box-folder 13/8)
  - Missoula Women’s Liberation Materials, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 13/9)
  - Photographs, One Woman Walkout, Helena, Montana, 1977 (Box-folder 13/10)
  - Posters, 1982-1992 (Box-folder OS 27)
  - Publications, Alterative Activism Booklets and Newsletters, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 13/11)
  - Publications, Articles, 1954-1972 (Box-folder 13/12)
  - Publications, Articles, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 13/13)
  - Publications, Booklets and Pamphlets, 1966-1970 (Box-folder 14/1)
  - Publications, Booklets and Pamphlets, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 14/2)
  - Publications, Employment Services Handbooks, 1982 (Box-folder 14/3)
  - Publications, Journals, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 14/4)
  - Publications, Journals, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 14/5)
  - Publications, Montana Divorce Handbook, Published by Department of Social Work/ Women’s Resource Center at UM, 1977 (Box-folder 14/6)
  - Publications, Montana Divorce Handbook, Published by Department of Social Work/ Women’s Resource Center at UM, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 14/7)
  - Publications, Women’s Work Flyers, undated (Box-folder 14/8)
  - Reports, Montana Legislative Council Report: Equality of the Sexes, 1974 (Box-folder 14/9)
  - VISTA, undated (Box-folder 14/20)
- Women's Lobbyist Fund, 1978-1999; Series VI; 2.0 linear feet
  - Administrative Records, 1984-1991; Subseries 1; 0.9 linear feet
    - Financial Statements, Minutes and Legislative Agendas, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 15/1)
    - Financial Statements, Minutes and Legislative Agendas, 1985 (Box-folder 15/2)
    - Financial Statements, Minutes and Legislative Agendas, 1986 (Box-folder 15/3)
    - Financial Statements, Minutes and Legislative Agendas, 1987 (Box-folder 15/4)
    - Financial Statements, Minutes, and Legislative Agendas, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 15/5)
    - Financial Statements, Minutes and Legislative Agendas, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 15/6)
    - Financial Statements, Minutes, and Legislative Agendas, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 15/7)
    - Correspondence, 1983-1993 (Box-folder 15/8)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1991 (Box-folder 15/9)
    - Long Range Planning, 6 audiocassettes, 1984, 1986 (Box-folder 25/4)
    - Membership and Readers Poll, 1985 (Box-folder 15/10)
    - Montana Women’s Lobby Fundraising Packet, 1990 (Box-folder 15/11)
    - Testimony, Press Releases, Clippings and Newsletters, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 15/12)
    - Testimony, Press Releases, Clippings and Newsletters, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 15/13)
    - Testimony, Press Releases, Clippings and Newsletters, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 15/14)
    - Testimony, Press Releases, Clippings and Newsletters, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 15/15)
    - Testimony, Press Releases, Clippings and Newsletters, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 15/16)
    - Testimony, Press Releases, Clippings and Newsletters, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 15/17)
    - Testimony, Press Releases, Clippings and Newsletters, undated (Box-folder 16/1)
    - Testimony, Press Releases, Clippings and Newsletters, undated (Box-folder 16/2)
    - Testimony, Press Releases, Clippings and Newsletters, undated (Box-folder 16/3)
    - Testimony, Press Releases, Clippings and Newsletters, undated (Box-folder 16/4)
    - Testimony, Press Releases, Clippings and Newsletters, undated (Box-folder 16/5)
    - Newsletters, 1987-1995 (Box-folder 16/6)
    - Photo Album, 1985-1988 (Box-folder OS 26)
  - Subject Files, 1978-1999; Subseries 2; 1.1 linear feet
    - Abortion Legislation, Montana Local Elections, Abortion Legislation, 1990 (Box-folder 16/7)
    - Abortion Legislation, Montana, 1990 (Box-folder 16/8)
    - AIDS Materials, 1990 (Box-folder 16/9)
    - Candidates for Governor, 1988 (Box-folder 16/10)
    - Conferences, Western States Women’s Agenda Conference, 1990 (Box-folder 16/11)
    - Deviate Sexual Conduct Act, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 16/12)
    - Deviate Sexual Conduct, Supreme Court Case, 1997 (Box-folder 16/13)
    - Deviate Sexual Conduct Law, Newspaper Clippings, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 16/14)
    - Diane Sands’ Lobbying License and Materials, 1981 (Box-folder 16/15)
    - Gay Rights, 1992–1996 (Box-folder 16/16)
    - Gay Rights, Gay and Lesbian Workplace Discrimination, 1994-1998 (Box-folder 16/17)
    - Gay Rights, Documents Regarding Workplace Discrimination Based on Sexual Orientation, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 16/18)
    - Gay Rights, Gay/Lesbian Newsletters, Articles, Documents, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 16/19)
    - Gay Rights, Newspaper Clippings, 1993 (Box-folder 16/20)
    - Governor’s Forum, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 16/21)
    - Governor’s Forum, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 16/22)
    - Insurance Project, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 17/1)
    - Insurance, Non-gender Insurance, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 17/2)
    - Insurance, Materials on Insurance Discrimination, 1987-1991 (Box-folder 17/3)
    - Legislation, Conflict and the Legislative Process, January 1993 (Box-folder 17/4)
    - Legislative Agenda, 3 audiocassettes, 1986 (Box-folder 25/5)
    - Legislative Session, 1 audiocassette, 1985 (Box-folder 25/6)
    - Legislature, Special Session, 1986 (Box-folder 17/5)
    - Montana Women’s Lobby Leadership Forum, 1992 (Box-folder 17/6)
    - Montana PRIDE Materials, 1992 (Box-folder 17/7)
    - Montana PRIDE Lawsuit, 1993 (Box-folder 17/8)
    - Montana PRIDE, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 17/9)
    - Montana PRIDE, Montana Fair Workplace Project Materials, 1993-1998 (Box-folder 17/10)
    - Montana PRIDE Basic Documents, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 17/11)
    - Montana PRIDE and Outspoken Newsletters, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 17/12)
    - Montana Women’s Agenda, 1992 (Box-folder 17/13)
    - Montana Women’s Campaign Network and Democratic Legislative Campaign Committee, Training Manual, 1995-1998 (Box-folder 17/14)
    - Montana Women’s Campaign Network, Democratic Campaign, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 17/15)
    - Montana Women’s Campaign Network, 1997 (Box-folder 17/16)
    - Montana Women’s Campaign Network, Directory, 1997 (Box-folder 17/17)
    - Montana Women’s Campaign Network, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 17/18)
    - Montana Women’s Campaign Network, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 17/19)
    - Montana Women’s Campaign Network, undated (Box-folder 17/20)
    - Montana Women’s Lobby, Legislative Hearings, Non-Gender Insurance, 4 audiocassettes, 1985 (Box-folder 25/7)
    - Newspaper Clippings, Homosexuality and Abortion, 1982-1992 (Box-folder 18/1)
    - Newspaper Clippings, Women’s Rights, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 18/2)
    - Photographs, 1980s-1990s (Box-folder 18/3)
    - Publications, a Guide to Montana’s Legislative Assembly and Report on Montana Children, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 18/4)
    - Publications, "The Women’s Caucus Across the Nation," and "Organizations for Women Legislators", undated (Box-folder 18/5)
    - Taxation Reform Materials, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 18/6)
    - Veteran’s Preference Special Session, 1983 (Box-folder 18/7)
    - Welfare Reform, 1987 (Box-folder 18/18)
    - Women’s Campaign School, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 18/19)
    - Women’s Campaign School, 1989-1992 (Box-folder 18/20)
    - Women’s Campaign School, undated (Box-folder 18/21)
    - Women’s Campaign School, Registration Forms, 1992 (Box-folder 18/22)
    - Women’s Campaign School, Evaluation Forms, undated (Box-folder 18/23)
    - Women’s Issues Congress, 1986 (Box-folder 18/24)
    - Women’s Suffrage, 75th Anniversary of Women’s Suffrage, 1995 (Box-folder 18/25)
    - Women’s Suffrage, Evaluations of 75th Anniversary of Women’s Suffrage, 1995 (Box-folder 18/26)
    - Women’s Suffrage, Susan B. Anthony Information, 1978-1983 (Box-folder 18/27)
    - Women’s Suffrage, Susan B. Anthony Information, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 18/28)
    - Women’s Suffrage, Susan B. Anthony Information, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 18/29)
    - Women’s Suffrage, Susan B. Anthony Information, 1993 (Box-folder 18/30)
    - Women’s Suffrage, Susan B. Anthony Information, 1994 (Box-folder 18/31)
    - Women’s Suffrage, Susan B. Anthony Information, 1994 (Box-folder 18/32)
    - Women’s Suffrage, Susan B. Anthony Information, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 18/33)
    - Women’s Suffrage, Susan B. Anthony Teaching Guide, 1983 (Box-folder 18/34)
- Montana Women's History Project, 1892-2000; Series VII; 1.9 linear feet
  - Correspondence, 1975-1987; Subseries 1; 0.3 linear feet
    - Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 19/1)
    - Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 19/2)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 19/3)
    - Correspondence to Sands, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 19/4)
    - MWHP History Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 19/5)
    - MWHP History Correspondence, 1977 (Box-folder 19/6)
    - Copies of "Silence No More," Letters, 1985 (Box-folder 19/7)
    - Thank You Letters from School Children, 1986 (Box-folder 19/8)
    - Women’s History Project Notes and Correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 19/9)
  - Oral Histories of Montana Women, 1920-1981; Subseries 2; 0.1 linear feet
    - Lou Alta Melton Merrill, 1920-1980 (Box-folder 19/10)
    - Hilda Smith, undated (Box-folder 19/11)
    - Fanny Sperry Steele, 1955 (Box-folder 19/12)
    - Hazel Wagner, Correspondence, Photos and Interview by Diane Sands for National Lesbian Archives, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 19/13)
    - Elizabeth Weldon Interview, 1976 (Box-folder 20/1)
    - Livingston/Bozeman Project, Correspondence and Notes, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 20/2)
  - Illegal Abortion in Montana Oral History Project, 1913-1999; Subseries 3; 0.3 linear feet
    - Articles and Reports, Article by Sands, "Using Oral History to Chart the Course of Illegal Clippings, from Adeline Beaver, 1984 (Box-folder 20/3)
    - Clippings, Maggie Smith Hathaway, 1913-1955 (Box-folder 20/4)
    - Grants, Application to Montana Council for the Humanities, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 20/5)
    - Interview, Transcripts of Interview with Bev Fisher, 1976 (Box-folder 20/6)
    - Interview, R.C. Line Interview, 1977 (Box-folder 20/7)
    - Interview, Anne Dunbar Interview by Diane Sands, 1981 (Box-folder 20/8)
    - Interview, Eleanor Mast Interview by Diane Sands, 1981 (Box-folder 20/9)
    - Interview, Kristina Fallan’s Story, undated (Box-folder 20/10)
    - Oral Histories, Background Information Sheets, Guidelines for Conducting Oral Interviews, undated (Box-folder 20/11)
    - Paper by Diane Sands, Drafts, "As American as Apple Pie: Illegal Abortion in Montana, 1880-1973", undated (Box-folder 20/12)
    - Prison Intake Record and Testimony RE: Illegal Abortion in Montana, 1936, 1940 (Box-folder 20/13)
    - Reports and Correspondence on Illegal Abortions, undated (Box-folder 20/14)
    - Research, Materials on Evelyn Cameron, 1900-1983 (Box-folder 20/15)
    - Research, Notes, Clippings, and Correspondence, 1922, 1989 (Box-folder 20/16)
    - Research, Annie Knipfer Personal Narrative, Poetry Booklet by Knipfer and Photograph, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 20/17)
    - Research, Articles, and Notes, Illegal Abortion, 1983 (Box-folder 20/18)
    - Research, Notes and Correspondence about Illegal Abortion, 1981, 1988 (Box-folder 20/19)
    - Research, Notes, Articles, and Papers, Abortion in Montana, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 20/20)
    - Research, Articles and Notes, Illegal Abortion, 1996 (Box-folder 20/21)
    - Research, Notes, undated (Box-folder 20/22)
  - Subject Files, 1911-1948, 1970-1987; Subseries 4; 0.7 linear feet
    - Articles and Notes, Madam Clarice Advice Column, 1911-1917 (Box-folder 20/23)
    - Diary of Mary Richardson Walker, June 10 – December 21, 1883, Published 1931 (Box-folder 20/24)
    - Clippings, The Women’s West Bibliography, and Student Papers, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 21/1)
    - Copy of Reminiscences of Clara Odden Currie, 1970 (Box-folder 21/2)
    - Articles and Notes, Copies of "Our Story, Herstory," and a paper by Diane Sands regarding Women’s Centers, 1971, 1976 (Box-folder 21/3)
    - Articles and Notes, Paper and Notes by Diane Sands, "A School for Politics: Roots of the Women’s Rights Movement in the Jacksonian Era," and Articles on Suffragist Movement, 1975 (Box-folder 21/4)
    - Bibliographies, 1976 (Box-folder 21/5)
    - Notes and Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 21/6)
    - Postcards, Pamphlets about Women, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 21/7)
    - Notebook and Publication, "Petticoat and Stethoscope" booklet, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 21/8)
    - Subject Files, 1977 (Box-folder 21/9)
    - Conference on Women in History, Correspondence, Syllabi, Bibliographies, 1977-1986 (Box-folder 21/10)
    - Bitterroot Resources for Women, Displaced Homemakers, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 21/11)
    - Pamphlets, Newsletters, Correspondence and Notes, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 21/12)
    - Project on the Status and Education of Women, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 21/13)
    - Booklet, "A Woman’s Place in Minnesota", 1981 (Box-folder 21/14)
    - Montana Post Newsletters, Oral History Guidelines, and Bibliography, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 21/15)
    - Newsletters and Notes, Montana Oral History Association and Plainswoman Newsletters, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 21/16)
    - Articles on Women’s Issues, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 22/1)
    - Women and the West Course Materials, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 22/2)
    - Women and the West Course Materials, 1984 (Box-folder 22/3)
    - Correspondence, Grant Application to Burlington Northern Foundation, Women’s Studies Topical Bibliographies, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 22/4)
    - Montana Women’s History Centennial Project, Committee for the Humanities Grant Application, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 22/5)
    - Flyers, Class Syllabi, and Bibliographies, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 22/6)
    - Pamphlets, Paper by Janet Kirkpatrick, "A Look at Unwed Pregnancy", 1983-1985 (Box-folder 22/7)
    - Pamphlets, Correspondence, Copy of "History News" and Women’s Resource Directory, 1984 (Box-folder 22/8)
    - ‘Harper and Row News," "Western Woman," and an Article on Oral History by Sherna Gluck, 1984 (Box-folder 22/9)
    - MWHP, 1984 (Box-folder 22/10)
    - Correspondence and Transcript of Diane Sands interview for Bozeman History Project, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 22/11)
    - Jeanette Rankin Dedication, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 22/12)
    - Correspondence, Autobiography of Esther Mace Stahl, Pamphlet and Notes, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 22/13)
    - Correspondence, Oral History Leaflet, Women’s History Newsletter, and Notes, 1982-1987 (Box-folder 22/14)
    - Information on Women’s Rights National Historical Park Correspondence and Newsletter, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 22/15)
    - Montana Committee for the Humanities Award, 1986 (Box-folder 22/16)
    - Notes and Brief Account of Library History Ennis, Montana, 1986 (Box-folder 22/17)
    - Notes, Articles, Correspondence and Interview Guidelines, 1987 (Box-folder 22/18)
    - Clippings, Pamphlet, Flyer, and Notes, 1987 (Box-folder 22/19)
    - Paper by Katherine M. Weist, "Nineteenth Century Observations of Northern Women", undated (Box-folder 22/20)
    - Paper by Sue Matthews, "Literature as ‘Hands-on’ Experience, undated (Box-folder 22/21)
    - Notes, undated (Box-folder 22/22)
    - Copies of Interview Transcripts and Notes, undated (Box-folder 22/23)
    - Women as Community Builders, 1 audiocassette, undated (Box-folder 25/8)
  - Publications, 1951-2000; Subseries 5; 0.4 linear feet
    - Archival Information and Bibliography, 1925, 1935 (Box-folder 22/24)
    - "Iron Teeth: A Cheyenne Old Woman", 1926 (Box-folder 22/25)
    - Articles on Feminism, 1951-1979 (Box-folder 22/26)
    - Reports on Women’s Issues, 1972-1979 (Box-folder 23/1)
    - Booklets, "Women in Colorado," and "Four Traditions: Women of New York During the American Revolution", 1974 (Box-folder 23/2)
    - Journals and Papers, 1974-1984 (Box-folder 23/3)
    - Frontiers: Journal of Women’s Studies, 1977, 1983 (Box-folder 23/4)
    - Susan B. Anthony Newspaper Clippings, 1979 (Box-folder 23/5)
    - Pamphlets on Women’s Rights Issues, 1979-1986 (Box-folder 23/6)
    - "Montana Post," and Montana Historical Society Newsletter, 1981 (Box-folder 23/7)
    - American Association of University Women Booklets, 1981-2000 (Box-folder 23/8)
    - "Notable Women of Montana," Stationary, 1984 (Box-folder 23/9)
    - Women’s History Network Directory and Montana Community for the Humanities Newsletter, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 23/10)
    - "Women’s History Network News," and "History Today" 1985 (Box-folder 23/11)
  - Photographs, 1892-1914; Subseries 6; 0.1 linear feet
    - Photos of Women and Families from Various Archives, 1892, 1897, 1905 (Box-folder 23/12)
    - Photos of Women and Families from the collection of the University of Montana Archives, 1914 (Box-folder 23/13)
    - Photos of Women and Families, 1914 (Box-folder 23/14)
    - Historical Pictures, undated (Box-folder 23/15)
- Newspaper Clippings, 1970-1995; Series VIII; 0.4 linear feet
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1970-1995 (Box-folder 24/1)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1970-1995 (Box-folder 24/2)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1970-1995 (Box-folder 24/3)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1970-1995 (Box-folder 24/4)
  - Veterans Preference Special Session, Dec 1983 (Box-folder 24/5)